[{"answer": "He has no one to blame but himself.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 11, "question": "So what does Sharon Bialek think now?", "qSentId": 10}, {"answer": "Well, first of all, let me just correct one thing you said.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 53, "question": "What do you think -- when it comes to the election battleground that you're a pivotal member of the -- of the Obama campaign, when you see this divide now being so clearly laid out, what do you think the average American is going to think of the debate?", "qSentId": 52}, {"answer": "Well, I think that the Republican Party has made a decision.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "Or has the president not played his hand very well?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, let me say a few things.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 78, "question": "What went wrong with the way that America used to do business so successfully?", "qSentId": 77}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I think part of -- if I were -- I'm not going to speak for him.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "Where are you most critical on yourselves?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "Well, it's hard to read because, as you say, it's been a really volatile situation.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "Who do you, when you're planning your campaign, most fear and perhaps are most, you know, looking forward to taking on?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "Well, you know, I want to watch this because I'm learning things about them every day, and it's a very interesting race.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "If I can give you Gingrich or Romney to take on the president, who would you prefer?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "Piers, you know me, you might think that I might have been elated at that.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 199, "question": "Sharon, what was your reaction when you heard that Herman Cain was suspending his campaign?", "qSentId": 198}, {"answer": "No, it's not.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 209, "question": "And you know the general feeling you got by the end was, well, he's only going because of the terrible media reporting all these outrageous lies, but it's not as simple as that, is it?", "qSentId": 208}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "I mean what is your financial position and has any of the motivation for what you've done been driven by the need for money?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "No, Piers, I was saddened for her, and I'm sure that she's very hurt in all this.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "ORGAN: Were you surprised to see, Gloria, Herman Cain's wife smiling and holding his hand as if nothing had happened given the volume of women who came forward with either harassment claims or in the case of Ginger White, the affair?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "You know, I listened to you last week, Piers, with the Lin Wood interview.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 246, "question": "I mean do you accept as some of Herman Cain's supporters say, indeed I interviewed his attorney Lin Wood about this, that there remains no hard evidence to substantiate what you say and in the end people have to kind of work out who they believe, you or him?", "qSentId": 245}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 265, "question": "Do you worry about the repercussions now?", "qSentId": 264}, {"answer": "Well, because unlike Britain, we actually have weather.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 314, "question": "Why are Americans so obsessed with weather?", "qSentId": 313}, {"answer": "There really is and -- which is why this is a great job.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 332, "question": "Somewhere in America at any given time there is this extremity of weather, isn't there?", "qSentId": 331}, {"answer": "Well, because I think, you know, it's kind of like -- again, another one of your well -- best loved Brits, Mary Poppins, I think once said, \"a spoonful of sugar helps the medicine go down, the medicine go down, the medicine go down.\"", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 343, "question": "Why do you think people love to hear bad news, which it normally is, from Al Roker?", "qSentId": 342}, {"answer": "Here's the deal: believe me, if I thought I was putting my life at risk, seriously, I would not do it.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 356, "question": "What's the matter with you?", "qSentId": 355}, {"answer": "I remember seeing Geraldo in the middle of a hurricane out to sea.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "And what would happen?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "There is that.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 367, "question": "And I wanted to Tweet into the show saying get out of the water would be plan B, wouldn't it?", "qSentId": 366}, {"answer": "I've spent about four months of a year here until this year.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "How long have you been here, Piers, in America?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "Well, look, you know, it's one of these things that I think I feel bad for Mitt Romney.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 390, "question": "What do you make of what's going on politically in your country?", "qSentId": 389}, {"answer": "I've been trying to get them to do that.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 417, "question": "It's about time they renamed that place the Roker-feller center, isn't it?", "qSentId": 416}, {"answer": "Well, look, personally, from just a standpoint -- from an American standpoint, from being an American, seeing this happen I think was just a momentous occasion in this country.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 437, "question": "What do you personally feel?", "qSentId": 436}, {"answer": "You know, it was a bet.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 457, "question": "To quote a famous chat show star in America, what was she thinking?", "qSentId": 456}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 468, "question": "It's going to be stormy today?", "qSentId": 467}, {"answer": "We do the same things everybody does.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What do you do to unwind?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 510, "question": "I want to come back after the break, Al, and talk about your book, this sinister tone that appears to be -- unless I'm wrong -- a kind of metaphor for you wanting to murder Matt Lauer?", "qSentId": 509}, {"answer": "Sometimes when he sees me punching, he kind of --", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 522, "question": "Does the president have to worry about the boxing part?", "qSentId": 521}, {"answer": "I was huge.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "You were gigantic, weren't you?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "No, Matt Lauer can have his job.", "docId": "111205pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "It's clearly a euphemism for you wanting Matt Lauer's job, isn't it?", "qSentId": 545}]